# **ELSPETH HUMBLE**

# Front End Developer

elspeth.humble@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/elspeth-humble https://github.com/spethstation

#### **PROFILE**

I am a meticulous and driven individual who takes pride in designing from the wireframe up. I enjoy responsive web design and have utilized my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React to build my own web applications from scratch. I also possess 12+ years of experience in graphic design & illustration.

#### **SKILLS**

- ✓ Programming languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- ✓ Libraries & Frameworks: React, Bootstrap, NPM, Node.js
- Programs & Tools: Visual Studio Code, Git & GitHub, Adobe Creative Suite, Figma
- ✓ Technical Skills: REST APIs, Responsive Web Design, SEO
- Soft Skills: Communication, problem-solving, adaptability, attention to detail, time management, collaboration

## **EDUCATION**

SheCodes (2022-2023)

Certificates: Introduction to Coding; Web Development; Responsive Web Development; React Development; Advanced React Development

Centre for Arts & Technology (2009-2011)

Graphic & Digital Media Design

NSCAD University (2004-2009)

Bachelor of Fine Arts, Major in Illustration

#### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

#### React Weather App (https://elspeth-weather-app-react.netlify.app/)

- Pulls live data from OpenWeatherMap API; includes search feature for location, weather conditions, and forecast
- Stack: VS Code, GitHub, Chrome, HTML/CSS/JS, Create React App, macOS

#### Portfolio (https://elspeth-portfolio.netlify.app/)

- · Personal website showcasing current and ongoing app, web, and design projects
- Stack: VS Code, GitHub, Chrome, HTML/CSS/JS, macOS

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Movella (formerly Kinduct Technologies)** | Executive Assistant & HR Coordinator

(2021-2022)

- Streamlined administrative tasks for CEO by managing 50+ emails per day and scheduling 15+ meetings /week, resulting in improvement in leadership efficiency
- Created new onboarding process and onboarded 40+ new hires, reducing recruitment timelines by 25%
- Transitioned 70+ employees to new group benefits plan and trained all staff on new HR policy information portal, increasing employee retention by 10%

### **One to One Wellness |** Office Administrator

(2019-2020)

- Shortened follow-up lead time resulting in higher percentage of repeat clientele and increase of fitness package sales
- Changed method of correspondence with third parties for AP/AR billing, resulting in quicker payment processing and a more streamlined month-end process
- Created a new digital patient record system and successfully archived 10+ years of client documentation, decreasing file management time for practitioners